Bohdan Tsap Developer cv.bohdaq.name

INFO

Highly competent sofware engineer capable of designing solutions from 'ground up'. Deep understanding of underlying technical stack alongside with knowledge of the basic computer science. More than 8 years of software engineering experience including frontend and backend.

SKILLS

- Team work
- · Collaboration
- Proactiveness

CONTACT

Cell: 38 063 03 86 173

Email: bohdan.tsap@tutanota.com

Lviv, Ukraine

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

CorporateServices.com (2016-2021)

Worked as a frontend lead in a small team on a product. Product purpose is to provide ability of a company incorporation in Singapore.

Core technologies: Polymer, lit-element, Firebase, Google Cloud, Spring, Git, Jenkins

ThinkTank.net (2014-2016)
Worked as a backend enginner in a dedicated team on a product. Product purpose is to provide ability of a collaboration and brainstorming for teams.
Core technologies: GWT, Spring, PostgreSQL, HTTP Long Pooling, Objective C, Git

Pics.io 2014

Worked as a frontend enginner on a startup. Startup purpose is to provide in-browser photo editing capabilities like in Lightroom. Core technologies: JavaScript, Git

WDS.co (2012-2014)

Worked as a Java developer. Took part in development projects related to mobile device managment and provisioning.

Core technologies: Java, Play Framework, OMA Device Management, Ruby on Rails, MySQL, Git

TECHNICAL SKILLS

A vision of how things are working on, from a physical layer up to application layer. Significant expertise in building, deploying and maintaining software. Hands on experience with setting up environments, releases and production support.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Lviv Polytechnic National University Bachelor of Computer Science (2010-2014)

Lviv Polytechnic National University Master of Computer Science (2014-2015)